That was my stomach.
What's your name?
It's Denji!
I need to tell you something right now.
From now on, you're in my care, Denji.
I expect "yes" or "woof" for answers.
I don't need a dog that says "no."
When you say that...
Someone in forensics once told me...
That when we get dogs that
aren't helpful, we put them down.
I thought she was nice.
I kind of liked her.
I had no idea she was scary like this.
Treating me like a damn dog...
I just remembered how Pochita's dead.
General
Falling objects can lead to huge accidents!!
Make sure anything on top of your car is securely tied down
We haven't had breakfast yet, either.
Let's grab something at the rest area.
Sorry, but I don't have any cash.
Just pick what you want. I'll pay.
And you're conspicuous
without a shirt on, so wear this.
Here.
All my life people have avoided me,
saying I'm filthy and smell bad.
No one's ever been nice to me before.
Much less a girl who looks this good!
I love her!
I'll take some udon...
Ramen
Udon • Soba
Curry Rice
Curry Udon
Corn Dog
Sausage
Udon and... a sausage!
Is that cool?
Sure is. I'll take a curry udon, please.
Coming up.
Oh, that sounds good, too...
Whoa, there.
Denji? You okay?
You smell good.
How much will it be?
Gimme one sec...
Denji?
Sorry about that!
It'll be 1,100 yen, all together.
The chainsaws cut me up, too,
Here's 2,000.
so I think I'm a little
low on blood right now.
How did you end up like this?
I had a pet devil, and he replaced my heart.
Kinda hard to believe, huh?
I don't really wanna believe it, either.
Pochita dying for my sake...
There's not a lot of precedent
for your condition,
even from a historical perspective.
It doesn't even have a name.
I believe you.
I've got a particularly good sense of smell.
So I can tell.
Your best friend is alive inside of you.
Not in the sentimental sense, either.
Your body has the scents
of both a human and a devil.
Is that right?
That's awesome!
Really... awesome...
Udon?!
The udon?
Is it cool if I eat my udon?
Are you all right?
Can you eat on your own?
I can...
I can not.
Here. Say, "Ahh."
Ahh...
Is it good?
Woof!
You are really sweet to be
enjoying soggy udon this much.
A lot like a dog, actually.
Um... what's your name?
Makima.
Miss Makima... is there a type
of guy you l-like?
I'm into the "Denji" type.
Denji?
Dude, that's me.
Is there a type of guy you like?
I'm into the "Denji" type.
I like you, too, Miss Makima.
Denji? This way, come on.
This is the Tokyo headquarters
for our Devil Hunters.
There are over a thousand Devil Hunters
in Tokyo, including civilians,
but Public Safety has the best benefits
and a lot of paid vacation time.
If Miss Makima likes me...
Then maybe, if we work together,
we'll eventually get together?
And if we get together...
we can get together, right?
I wanna! I wanna get together
with her real bad!
Denji...
Yeah?
We're supposed to
wear uniforms, so put this on.
Once you've changed,
I'll introduce you to a coworker.
This is Aki Hayakawa. He started
three years before you, Denji.
You're going to be shadowing him today.
I'm not working with you, Miss Makima?
That should be obvious.
You're not even in her league.
Time for patrol.
No! Miss Makima!
Damn it, get up.
No way! I wanna work with Miss Makima!
If you do a good job,
we can work together someday.
So, do that, okay?
Hey, big man.
Does Miss Makima have a boyfriend?
Hey, come on.
Hey!
Come with me.
You need to quit this job.
Show up tomorrow,
and I'll kick your ass again.
Why, though?
Look, I'm trying to be nice, here.
People who start this job without
thinking it through end up dead.
I've had colleagues who got
into devil hunting for the payday,
and it got them all killed by devils.
The survivors are the ones
with real motivation.
You're just after Makima, right?
That's why you took the job?
Ding-ding!
Then I'm glad I hit you.
I'll let her know that you ran off,
scared away by the devils.
You really are a nice guy, huh?
Because... when I fight a dude...
It's nuts... or nothing!
I had udon for the first time today, man.
A sausage, too.
Got treated like a decent
human being for the first time,
and even had someone pay for my meal.
It's like a dream come true for me.
I didn't really think it through
when I started devil hunting,
but if I get to keep up this kind of life?
I don't care if it kills me.
Actually, y'know, I take it back.
It's not just my life, anymore.
Makima...
is not the kind of woman
a punk like you should be chasing!
What the hell are you saying?
Sounds to me like you just like her, too!
You... really did...
Only aim... for my balls...
Shit.
The big guy's testicles were attacked
by the Nut Devil, ma'am!
That's a lie. He's lying.
So, do you think you two can work together?
No way!
He's a piece of trash!
I'm glad you two are hitting it off.
Denji, you're going to
be joining Hayakawa's unit.
Unit?
This punk?!
I've already got enough
troublemakers, don't I?
Adding another... I don't know...
I told you when I put it together, right?
Your team's an experimental one,
operating differently from the usual method.
What exactly is he, ma'am?
Denji's human, but can
transform into a devil.
Damn right! Pretty sweet, huh?
And that's the truth?
I always figured those stories
were baseless rumors.
He's special.
Which is why he's going to be
receiving special treatment.
If he tries to resign,
or becomes insubordinate...
Denji will be disposed of as a devil.
Uh, what's that mean?
It means we're working
together until you die.
You're going to be living with me
so I can keep an eye on you.
Just remember, they said I can
kill you if you try to run off.
Hey, is Miss Makima a bad person?
If you think that's the case,
then give up on her.
If you're really a devil, you should
just be grateful she doesn't kill you.
We're Devil Hunters, got that?
So, she's a good person, then?
Of course she is.
She saved my life.
Miss Makima...
I hope I get to hug her again.
Strawberry jam, plum jam, orange jam...
Then some butter and honey, plus...
Let's throw some cinnamon on, too.
I got the best toast ever right here!
So good!
It's freaking fantastic!
How long are you gonna be in there?!
Don't fall asleep on the toilet!
A Fiend has been reported
in an east Nerima residence.
Civilian evacuation and cordon
are both complete.
The Fiend in question has
holed up in a second story room.
We'll leave it to you
Devil Hunters from here.
Is this a new rookie, Hayakawa?
Hey, what's a Fiend?
Did you never go to school or something?
Nah, man, no.
When a devil takes control
of a human corpse, you get a Fiend.
Wait, doesn't that make me a Fiend?
No. Fiends always have characteristic heads.
Should be obvious enough once we see him.
The devil controls a Fiend's personality.
You kill this one.
Turn into a devil,
and show me what you can do.
That'll help me figure out
if you're of any use.
Don't look at me...
You're dead! Dead, dead, dead!
Damn Devil Hunters!
Hey. Why didn't you use your devil powers?
Thing is...
When I kill devils with my powers,
they get real messed up.
So, like... I coulda ended up
like this Fiend, right?
So I kinda... wanted to
make it painless for him.
All right. Listen to me.
Fiends are just like any other devil.
If you're hunting them,
then drop the sympathy.
My entire family was killed
by a devil right in front of me.
I've had drinks with the cops down below.
They're risking their lives
to protect their wives and kids.
Everyone is serious about this except you.
I'd rather make any devil I kill
suffer as much as possible.
What are you trying to do?
Make friends with them?
If there's a devil I could be
friends with, then yeah, I would.
'Cuz I don't have any friends.
I'll remember that.
Guess I pissed him off...
I was just trying to keep
blood off these dirty magazines.
When the chainsaws are out, blood gets
everywhere and makes a real mess.
I made it easy for you,
so I get to keep these!
Okay, the porn is secured.
I want you to show me your dream.
I'm pretty serious about this, Pochita.
I'm already living the dream,
just like our bargain said.
I'll remember that.
My dream might've come true already,
but he must be chasing his.
I get to bathe every day, eat good food...
Get to hang around a hot chick...
My life's a 10 outta 10, but it feels
like something's missing.
Am I missing something? Something that'd
give me a real perfect score?
He's gotta be after some revenge shit.
They're trying to protect their families.
I wonder if Miss Makima
is after anything like that?
Miss Makima...
I wanna touch her boobs.
Touching boobs is a dream I gave
up on a long time ago,
but I've got a real job now.
Maybe I could pull it off?
I probably couldn't score
with a girl just yet.
But boobs?
If I had the right plan, and the
willpower, then maybe...
Everyone is serious about this except you.
So that's what he meant!
I've found it! Something to be serious about!
My goal! It's...
Boobs!
Boobs?
Hey! Pay attention, dumbass!
Listen to what?
I'm assigning you a partner
starting today, Denji.
Partner?
As a precaution, Public Safety executes patrols
and smaller missions with two-person teams.
This is great timing. She's here.
Be careful. She's a Fiend.
Prostrate yourselves, humans!
For I am Power!
Are you to be my so-called partner?!
Power?! Your name's Power?!
And you're a Fiend?!
Are Fiends allowed to be Devil Hunters?!
Well, whatever! Nice to meet you!
Fiends, like devils,
are targets for extermination.
But Power's highly rational,
so she's been on Hayakawa's team.
I mentioned this before,
but Public Safety Devil Extermination
Special Division 4 is an experimental unit.
The higher-ups will be looking
to dissolve your team as soon as possible
if you can't get results.
I don't need to explain what would happen
to you two if that happens, do I?
Power's horns stand out a bit too much,
so you'll want to patrol areas
without a lot of pedestrians.
Human! Provide me with something
to kill immediately!
I am starved for blood!
I can put up with crazy,
as long as she's hot enough.
The question is, how do I get
my hands on those boobs?
If you run into any civilian Devil Hunters,
or the police try to question you
about what you're doing...
We've got a pair of suspicious individuals...
Excuse me, I need to ask you—
We're with Public Safety Devil
Extermination Special Division 4.
...say that, show them your ID,
and they'll make a sour face
and leave you alone.
Where the hell are all the devils?!
This is likely my fault!
Before becoming a Fiend,
I was a devil that was feared by all!
Demonic peons will likely flee
the moment they catch my scent!
Wait, how are we gonna
get anything done, then?!
If you have any questions,
just ask Hayakawa.
He's the one who put you two together.
That asshole! He set me up!
He stuck me with Power
so I can't do anything cool!
He's trying to get me fired!
The scent of blood!
Whoa! Hey, crazy, where you going?!
The game is afoot!
The battle is joined!
Damn, she's fast!
The scene's evacuated and blocked off.
It's the Sea Cucumber Devil.
Yes, the Sea Cucumber Devil.
Requesting backup
in front of Nerima Station.
I said, it's the Sea Cucumber—
Do you know what a sea cucumber is?
Look, I'm trying to say—
What the...?
Did you see?! The kill is mine!