Just one.
I'm not smoking. It's bad for your bones.
I wish you would. I get the feeling
we're gonna be together for a while.
Just one, then.
This is the first and last
cigarette I ever light up.
Yes! Let me get that for you.
You're kind of awful, making
someone who's underage smoke.
You're underage?!
Yeah...
Well, you obviously can't smoke, then!
Hand it over.
I'll hang onto this one for you, then.
Once you grow up and you're ready
to develop an addiction, I'll give it back.
The Ghost Devil doesn't have eyes,
so it uses fear to see.
Himeno explained that to me.
Himeno...
I'll be with you soon.
Snake—
Don't kill her.
Kobeni, why'd you stay with Public Safety?
Bonuses are coming up soon, so...
Barf!
Meat is meat!
It matters not if it is porcine,
bovine, or human!
It sure as hell does!
We're here to catch that Samurai Sword dude.
You better not try to eat him when we do.
Damn it...
They haven't noticed us.
Don't make any noise.
I am the one called Power!
These, I can defeat.
Have at thee!
After me, Denji!
I entrust my back to you!
How's that?! What say you now?!
I have not fled!
I am proud! I am beautiful!
A fierce foe...
Denji! Bear witness,
and then speak of this day!
For it is Power who is the greatest of all!
Found you, Sideburns Man.
Hold up a second, will you?
Let's have a chat.
Depending on how you play this,
we're willing to turn ourselves in.
We just want satisfaction, you get it?
Denji... you killed their friends,
and my granddad.
We just want you to atone for that.
I only killed their pals and your grandpa
because they turned into zombies, dude.
Don't you fucking lie!
Dumbass little shits like you
always try and lie!
Y'know what? Fine.
Even if that's true...
Those zombies used to be people, too.
You seriously don't feel bad,
after killing them?
Sure don't.
Sawatari's put me through the ringer, too.
Apparently my heart was replaced
with the Katana Devil.
But even I have trouble sleeping
on nights when I've accidentally
killed zombies, man.
Looks like you're the only one
whose heart's not human anymore.
If you've got any kind of conscience left...
Just let us kill you.
Nah.
Okay.
Then I'm gonna cut you to pieces!
Go ahead and try, dumbass!
What?!
I thought you were gonna cut me up!
How about it?!
Die!
Damn it...
You're looking sharper than before...
Denji, what are you even fighting for?
To protect the life I've got now, I guess?
Public Safety got you living
the good life, is that it?
Gotta put up with a nag and a brat...
But I like it pretty good.
Which is why I've gotta kick your ass,
so Ms. Makima will praise me.
You can't beat me, man.
What, you think you've got me beat already?
I ain't dead yet!
You trash!
Where the hell is he?
Due to an incident in one of the cars,
Get... off!
the train will now come
to an emergency stop.
The doors will open, so please
evacuate in an orderly fashion.
I repeat, due to an incident
in one of the cars...
Aw, come on, dude!
Look... can we ban that move? Seriously.
Keep yapping.
You're done.
Can't even fight anymore.
How about it, Denji?
Care to apologize for killing
Granddad before you die?
I can still fight.
I've still got a chainsaw on my head!
Dumbass!
Didn't Granddad teach you...
About when to know when you're beat?
Beg for his forgiveness,
and I'll make it quick.
You went right after my head...
Thanks for that, dipshit!
Didn't the geezer teach you...
that beasts shouldn't trust
anything a hunter says?!
Guess you're awake.
You really are like me, huh?
Pulled that katana out of your arm,
and the halves of your body
stuck back together.
I'll kill you...
You're fucking dead!
Losers sure love to make noise, huh?
We've got a while until
the cops show up to grab you.
And to be honest,
I'm not really satisfied yet.
You killed Himeno.
That's one less hot lady in the world,
thanks to your stupid ass.
But you don't seem to care, and you'll
get to spend the rest of your life in jail.
How am I supposed to deal with that?
Not like you can do anything about it.
You're just Public Safety's lapdog!
We're about to have us a contest.
Contest?
Hey, great timing.
This is Hayakawa from Division 4.
Target is restrained on the train tracks in front of the clock tower.
Requesting backup.
You wanna get in on this, too, Hayakawa?
It's gonna be the best contest ever.
What the hell are you talking about?
See, he shot at Himeno...
So I figure we get to take shots at him.
That's why we'll make it a contest.
We take turns giving him nut shots,
and whoever gets him to scream the loudest
before the cops show up is the winner.
What are you, psycho?!
You in or what?
Our job is to catch this guy.
Not torture him to make
ourselves feel better.
It's not like Himeno would've wanted that.
That right?
So...
What do I get if I win?
His family jewels, of course!
Hey...
Hang on, hang on!
Don't do it, come on—
Car #2
Metro PD
Himeno... Can you hear this up in heaven?
We're playing a requiem for you.
These terrorist attacks
were arranged by Akane Sawatari,
a Devil Hunter formerly
from the private sector.
She had a contract with the Gun Devil,
and distributed guns to the yakuza.
In exchange, Sawatari was told
to recover the Chainsaw Devil's heart.
And why exactly was Sawatari
after the Chainsaw Devil's heart?
Before we were able to question her...
Suicide?
Triggered automatically by the terms
of her contract with the Gun Devil, maybe.
We were able to recover 1.4 kilograms
of Gun Devil flesh from the building.
After combining that with the
five kilograms held by Public Safety,
the flesh chunk has finally begun
to move toward the main body.
Then the time has come...
Where is it headed toward?
I have this dream all the time.
I always have it,
and then I always forget it.
Denji.
Pochita?
Pochita, come on out!
I can at least pet you in a dream.
Denji.
You can't open that door.
Tell me, Denji...
Between the country mouse
and the city mouse...
Which would you rather be?