You're gonna contract
with the devil in this room, Aki.
It's the Future Devil.
There are two people in Public Safety
that have contracts with it.
One had to give up half their lifespan...
The other gave both their eyes,
along with their sense of taste and smell.
Hopefully it likes you,
and you'll get a bargain.
Well, go right on in.
The future rules.
The future rules...
The future rules!
Yeah, yeah!
The future rules! The future rules!
You shout, "The future rules," too! Come on!
I'm here to make a deal with you.
Tell me what you want from me.
You've got a real shitty attitude, man!
Whatever. Let's take a peek at that future!
What I see will help me decide on the trade.
Stick your head into my gut already!
How else am I supposed to see your future?
Here's how it's gonna work:
I'm gonna live inside your right eye.
That way, I can lend you my power.
That look is asking, "Is that really all?"
Well, the reason is: Your death
in the future will be the fucking worst.
Wanna know how it happens? You're gonna—
Doesn't matter.
I'm not interested in how I die,
as long as I can kill my targets.
The rest doesn't matter.
Now, get in my eye.
Okay.
You get full points
for your moves on that one.
We don't need to do this
every day from now on.
Let's cut back to once a week.
Aw, yeah...
We did it...
You've gotta make sure your brain keeps
its cool, even when you're feeling high.
Never forget your situation,
and the weapons available to you.
Tomorrow, we're gonna try some
live combat with an eye toward training.
What manner of combat?
We're all gonna grab the Snake Devil
woman and Samurai Sword
that got Himeno and the others.
It's gonna be the rollout
of the all-new Division 4.
If the op goes bad, the division is done for.
Which means you two get disposed of
in a for-real battle with me.
If it comes to that, I'll show some
mercy and let you live, teach.
You made me stronger, after all.
I can kill more devils because of you.
And that means I've got my ticket
to hooking up with Makima!
I appreciate you making the time for this,
with your busy schedule.
I hope you'll continue
to instruct Denji and Power.
I'm sick of them already.
Whenever the hunting dogs I train end
up dead, I find myself drinking more.
I figured I wouldn't mind what
happened to a pair of toys, but...
Must be old age. Now I'm even
getting attached to them.
You mentioned that you
wanted to discuss something?
The assault that hit the Special Division.
Public Safety isn't exactly clueless.
You knew it was going to happen,
and didn't try to stop it, right?
I came under attack too, remember?
I don't care what fucked up
shit you have cooking,
or how many of my hunting
dogs you get killed.
You get a pass as long as you're
serving mankind's interests.
But only in that case.
All I want is to save as many people
as possible from devils.
If this operation is a success,
Division 4's existence
will actively become part
of the public record.
That'll give us more freedom, and we'll be
able to save even more people from devils.
You liar.
The boss has got a separate
team escorting him.
We should move you, too.
Nowhere in Japan is safe,
as long as Makima's alive.
We're ready for them if they strike here.
So, pipe down.
Shut up, bitch!
Sir...
Granddad would've never let us run.
...
Besides, that piece of shit
Denji is in Division 4.
I'm gonna carve out his heart next time.
The rest of you don't need
to worry about the big guy.
Even if he dies, he can be brought back.
But if you're staying here, you need
to be careful about getting bitten.
Bitten?
What're you talking about?
We've got a secret weapon stored below us.
A little parting gift from Granddad...
An army of zombies made up of deadbeats
who couldn't pay their debts.
A human who gets bitten
by a zombie becomes a zombie.
We'll use them to finish Division 4 off.
We're gonna do a bit of sightseeing
and then head back to Kyoto.
We'll probably never meet again,
so there's something I wanted to ask you.
I've heard you're after the Gun Devil, Aki.
You seriously think you can kill that thing?
You just lost to folks who managed
to kill around 20 Public Safety agents.
And you think you've got a shot
against a freak who took down
millions of people all over the world?
To be honest, we ended up in Public Safety
because of a beef with the Gun Devil, too.
But we're not trying to kill it.
Just gotta think for a second
to realize how impossible that is.
If I'm being real, just looking
at you kinda pisses me off, Aki.
Weak as you are, you go around
with this hotshot goal,
like some kinda manga character.
It's so lame, it gives me goosebumps.
Literally. Can you see them?
Sure can't.
I really don't care what you have to say.
You can sit back and watch.
And if I lose and end up dead,
go ahead and laugh.
I know I'm not being realistic about
what I can accomplish right now.
But I also know that I couldn't
keep going, any other way.
I appreciate your help.
Hey, Aki!
You might piss me off,
but I'm rooting for you.
So here's one last bit of advice:
"Everyone who works in the Special Division
is crazy, so watch yourself!"
We've got a guest from Public Safety.
Get the good stuff for her.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Well, I heard about our younger
guys popping off in Tokyo.
I figure I owe you any answers I've got.
I want you to understand
that it wasn't on my orders.
From what I've heard, this Sawatari
woman's the one behind it.
She was the contact that hooked these kids
into deals involving the Gun Devil.
What kind of deals?
They give the Gun Devil 20,000 yen,
and they get guns and ammo in exchange.
Fancy that, devils needing money.
They're not so different from us, after all.
I need you write down the names
of everyone in your organization
that has a contract with the Gun Devil.
Yeah, no problem.
Throw them in the slammer for a while,
give them something to think about.
I'll also need the names from other
families, as well. Not just yours.
Miss, you're not getting
the big picture here.
If I did that, and the other families
found out, it'd mean war.
It'd be real stupid.
It's for the safety of the public.
I'm requesting your cooperation.
You ever hear the term
"necessary evil" before, miss?
What happens if we end up
wiping each other out?
All it does is open up Japan
to foreign mafia.
I'm not gonna deny
that we get up to bad business.
But the Chinese and Soviet mobs
make us look like angels.
And we're the ones keeping them away.
Just like how Devil Hunters
keep people safe from devils...
The yakuza are keeping
Japan safe from foreigners.
Though I hear there's a lot of
uneducated types in your line of work,
so maybe you just don't get it.
It's gonna take more than a bribe
to get me to snitch, lady.
This isn't money.
It's a collection of things that belong
to associates of everyone here.
Parents, grandparents,
siblings, lovers, wives...
Their eyes.
Eyes?
Please, relax.
Public Safety has someone
who can return these safely.
In exchange for your cooperation,
I can introduce you.
You bitch—
When you talk about "necessary evil,"
you're using that term to justify
the evil acts you commit.
Society doesn't need your excuses.
It's not a true necessary evil
unless the nation itself is holding
the leash and maintaining control.
The police and Devil Extermination Division 2
have the basement and first
entrances floor surrounded.
They're leaving the actual raid
to Special Division 4.
We're going to kill as many of them
as possible, and steal Denji's heart.
If we use Snake after that's done, the two
of us should make it out of here okay.
I'm gonna kill Denji.
Don't get too worked up.
I wanna go home.
So why don't you, then?
After all that training I did...
I'm gonna slaughter Sideburns Man!
Our minds have been honed, after all!
This shall prove a simple matter!
I hate this.
What's the plan?
No plan.
The entire Special Division goes in.
Excuse me?
I'm Shiina, with the Kanagawa
prefectural PD.
I'm Furuno, with Devil
Extermination Division 2.
Name's Kishibe. I'm Captain
of Special Division 4.
The police and Division 2 just need to keep
the entrances to the first floor
and basement sealed off.
The Special Division will
take out the terrorists inside.
There's one thing you need
to be careful about, though:
Special Division 4 is comprised
almost entirely of non-humans.
If any of them get loose in the city,
it'll mean worse casualties
than the terrorists could've caused.
I'm gonna explain their
unique characteristics,
because you need to be prepared to
engage with them. Not the terrorists.
Zombies! Zombies!
It's all-I-can-eat!
There's the Shark Fiend.
He can swim inside any surface,
including walls and floors.
He can also transform into his devil form
for brief periods of time.
Oh, sorry about that!
Since you went for a bite,
I thought you were a zombie!
The Violence Fiend.
Normally, becoming a Fiend makes
a devil weaker than they were...
But even as a Fiend, this one's dangerous enough
that we make the Violence Fiend wear
a mask that dispenses poison gas.
That mask stays on, no matter what.
Hey, lady? You might wanna run for it.
If these guys bite humans,
they turn into zombies.
Oh! You're a devil, huh?
The Spider Devil.
Most of the time she assumes a human form.
Humanoid devils tend to be friendly,
but at the end of the day,
they're still devils.
They'll kill you for looking at them funny.
Ugh... it got on my shoes.
This seriously sucks.
The Angel Devil.
Bit of a special case:
No enmity towards humans,
but you'll wanna keep your distance.
Physical contact means
your lifespan gets drained away.
Hey, can I ask you something?
You got a handkerchief I could borrow?
I'm impressed you came this close,
since I can shorten your life with a touch.
It's okay so long as material
breaks the contact, right?
Ow, ow...
Devil, take this one outside.
He gave me an order...
But I'll take that over fighting, I guess.
You two.
We'll let the Fiends handle this.
Let's find Samurai Sword
and the Snake woman.
You know where to look or something?
No. We'll split up, and search.
Come along quietly—
Snake:
Spit it out.
Damn it...
Ghost. Kill him.
Looks like he's gotten a little better...
If you use my power, you'll be able
to peek a bit into the future.
But that's all.
Choke him to death.